Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/farahadilla-5462403b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Editing
Journalism
Newspapers

Languages

Malay (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual) French (Elementary)

Farah Adilla

Business Journalist at New Straits Times Kuala Lumpur

Summary

Experienced Business Journalist with a demonstrated history of working in the newspapers industry. Skilled in Storytelling, News Writing, Event Management, Editing, and Journalism. Strong media and communication professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Marine Sciences from Universiti Malaysia Terengganu.

Experience

New Straits Times Business Journalist February 2016 - Present (5 years 11 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Spring News
Foreign Correspondent
June 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months)
Bangkok Metropolitan Area, Thailand

The Malaysian Reserve Writer December 2010 - January 2016 (5 years 2 months) Kuala Lumpur

Sedia Teguh Sdn Bhd Application Engineer March 2009 - December 2010 (1 year 10 months) Kuala Lumpur

Education

Universiti Malaysia Terengganu Bachelor's Degree, Marine Sciences · (2004 - 2007)